<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Lachlan Deer</title>
    <link>/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Lachlan Deer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me I am a Postdoctoral Fellow in the Marketing Group at University of Chicago Booth School of Business. I recently completed my PhD in Economics at the University of Zurich.
My current research leverages text as data, utilizing tools from Machine Learning and Natural Language Processing, integrating their outputs into quantitative models to understand:
 The impact of social media content on consumer demand for new products The interaction between offline advertising and online word of mouth How the structure of online networks influence the spread of information and decision making  I&amp;rsquo;m on the job market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Current Research</title>
      <link>/home/publications_selected/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/publications_selected/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/home/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/publications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working Papers</title>
      <link>/home/working_papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/working_papers/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Progress</title>
      <link>/home/wip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/wip/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>/home/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Teaching @ UZH As an Instructor:
 Programming Practices for Research in Economics: Foundations, 1st year PhD Course.
 Co-taught with Julian Langer 2019 Edition: Course Home Page, Course Material &amp;amp; Installation Guide
  Programming Practices for Research in Economics, 2nd year PhD Course.
 Co-taught with Adrian Etter, Julian Langer and Max Winkler
 2017 Edition: Course Home Page, Course Material &amp;amp; Installation Guide
 2016 Edition: Drop me an email for the detailed material.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code</title>
      <link>/home/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/software/</guid>
      <description> R Packages Empirical IO demandr: Nested Logit Demand Estimation with Aggregate Market Shares  Estimate Nested Logit Demand models on aggregate market share data Coauthored with Christian Oertel (U Zurich) Status: Under development Code: available on Github  Econometrics hayshir: R Companion to &amp;ldquo;Econometrics&amp;rdquo; by Fumio Hayashi  Provides all data sets used in textbook, and companion code to each chapter in text Website Code: available on Github  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous</title>
      <link>/home/miscellaneous/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/miscellaneous/</guid>
      <description>Installation Guide for Software and Packages While teaching programming skills I have assembled a set of instructions for setting up a computing environment that I find useful for economics / marketing research. Instructions are provided for Linux (Ubuntu flavored), Mac and Windows environments.
 Installation Guide  Borrowed and updated from the programming course I co-taught at UZH in 2017.   Reproducible Research Workflows The Snakemake workflow management system helps to create reproducible and scalable data analyses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>